the code in this problem
is very similar to our last problem
however
we've added a little bit of code on line
five
you can see that on line five after we
invoke the integer times method we've
placed the integer
10. we can still expect that our
count sheet method will output 0 through
4 when we invoke the times method
but now the return value of our count
sheet method that we output on line 8
will be different our call to integer
times
is no longer the last line executed in
the count sheet method
after ruby has finished executing our
call to times
and has output 0 through 4
line 5 of our count sheet method will be
executed
the evaluated result of the integer 10
is simply the integer 10 so that's what
we can expect the return value of our
method to b
so when we run our code this time we'll
expect that the call to put s
on line 3 will output 0
1 2 3 and 4 while the call to put s on
line eight
outputs ten
and that's what we see
you